I killed Chung B.
No, I killed Chung.
Arrest me. Go ahead...
Grandma, I love you.
Yes, I need a car,
from Ko Cho Village to Wan Mei Village.
My wife didn't kill Chung B. I did.
What? Why did you do it?
Chi, why are you saying this?
We'll take Cheung Wang-chi's statement
in the presence of a social worker.
You must all go back to the Police station
for yours.
The cops are downstairs.
They'll bring me in for questioning.
Remember what I told you before?
If the Police ask you something
you can't answer,
what should you do?
Say nothing.
Good.
Just do what I told you to do.
When you get to the Police station,
first you make a scene
then complain about chest pain
and ask to be sent to the hospital.
Once you get there, just tell them
you want to see me alone.
Chi, the Police found out
we went to Chung's village house.
We can't hide anymore.
You don't want to see me and
the baby go to jail, right?
It's time you tell the Police
what I told you before.
I must protect you.
I want Chung B to reincarnate
and be our son again.
I have taught him for so long,
Chi should know what to tell the Police.
The Police should believe Chi hated Chung
and wanted to kill this illegitimate son.
One day, Chung B called me and told me...
no, I told him I wanted to see him.
He gave me the address
so I took a taxi there with my wife.
Inside, we had a fight.
my wife was so pissed, she left.
I was angry he pissed off his mother.
I told him he was an illegitimate child
and should have no claim on
my father's assets.
He was so angry that I didn't believe him
he had a seizure.
I saw a sugarcane and wanted to save him.
I stuck it down his mouth
so he won't bite his tongue.
But he hit me
and flung his arms and legs around.
I forced the sugarcane in further
and after a while he died.
Then what happened?
My wife came back inside.
How come Chung B is not moving?
He's dead.
My wife knew I killed Chung B by mistake
and didn't want me to go to jail.
The bag had my fingerprints on it,
we must remove it.
We also took the bag with the papers
dividing up the money.
After we packed everything...
Let's go.
we flagged down a taxi nearby and paid cash.
We went home and pretended
we never went out.
That's all.
Why didn't you tell us sooner?
I don't want my wife to go to jail.
Didn't you complain about chest pain?
You seem fine as soon as your wife shows up.
Why did you suddenly turn yourself in?
Did your wife tell you in the room
to take the rap for her?
No! I killed Chung B!
I did...I killed Chung B!
It wasn't her fault.
Relax...
Did your wife tell you to put
Chung Siu-chung's smart watch
in your mother's bedroom?
No.
I didn't want Mom to regret throwing away
Chung's belonging.
Also...I put the jacket in Mom's room.
Not my wife.
My husband has the mental age
of an 8-year-old.
He didn't mean to kill Chung.
I'm his wife, I can't tell on him
and let him go to jail.
You knew Cheung Wang-chi was
connected to Cheung Siu-chung's death,
why did you tell the Police
Tang Suk-han is a suspect
and made us look for her jacket?
I only found out later she was
at the village house.
I never got along with my mother-in-law.
I'd rather you arrest her.
I must protect my husband.
Where is the second trust fund document?
I burnt it.
Though Chang Wang-chi has the
mental age of an 8-year-old,
and claims he hated Cheung Siu-chung,
his reaction at the mourning hall
told a different story.
Leung Yuet-ping taught her husband
to recite those lines
and take the rap for her
with a seamless story.
This woman is something else.
Sze Sir, Right Sir, you asked me
to check on the taxi driver.
I found something.
The driver you found didn't even drive
the taxi that night.
That's why you got nothing from him.
The real driver's last name was Tsang.
He just gave his statement.
What did he say?
He said he drove Leung Yuet-ping
and Cheung Wang-chi
from Ko Cho Village to Wan Mei Village.
Cheung Wang-chi was mentally challenged
but married such a pretty wife.
That's why he remembered them well.
That means Cheung Wang-chi was there.
There's a chance he was telling the truth.
Sir, let us post bail for Chi.
He can't go to jail, he'll die.
Grandma, Dad is in custody, not jail.
What's the difference? He's still locked up.
Oh dear, he can't be left alone.
Ms. Leung, sign here and you may go.
You tramp! Chi couldn't have killed Chung.
You taught him to take the rap for you.
Watch your mouth!
Chung is my son, why would I kill him?
Now that I'm carrying Chi's baby,
I don't want him to go to jail either.
I wish he didn't kill Chung.
But he used too much force.
I wish I was inside at the time.
I could have intervened.
Leung Yuet-ping, quit your act.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
I really don't want to start an argument.
Sir, if there's nothing else. I'm leaving.
You may go.
Mrs. Cheung, this is a search warrant
for us to search your house.
After Chung died,
I saw Chi in the backyard by himself
throwing paper airplanes around.
Chung B, did you get the airplanes?
Looks like Dad put down in drawing
the times he spent with Chung.
I got it.
Is this a drawing by Chi of Chung
when he died?
Looks like it.
That means Leung Yuet-ping
was there when Chung died.
She had a hand in forcing the
sugarcane into Chung's mouth.
Look at this!
The drawing is crude
and there's nothing in the background.
It's hard to say this is
the scene of the crime.
The woman in the drawing could be
pulling out the sugarcane
instead of forcing it in.
Though this paper airplane
can't prove anything.
Cheung Wang-chi was throwing
paper airplanes at the mourning hall
he was communicating with Cheung Siu-chung.
He wasn't angry with him.
But Cheung Wang-chi already admitted
he killed Cheung Siu-chung while
trying to save him.
Nothing will make a difference.
No...if we can verify
the woman in the drawing was Leung Yuet-ping
at least we're sure of one thing.
She was there when Chung died.
Why did she lie?
The most likely reason was
she had a hand in forcing the
sugarcane into Chung's mouth.
I know this drawing is not solid evidence,
but at least it's a lead.
That's very true, Sir...
We can ask Cheung Wang-chi about
this paper airplane.
What was he trying to draw?
Where and what happened?
I don't know.
Dad won't say anything.
He doesn't know anything.
He's driving me crazy.
Chi has been brainwashed.
He only listens to that woman
and took the blame for everything.
It's hopeless.
Come on, Grandma. Don't worry!
There's still time before the trial.
I will find evidence to help Dad.
Here's $5M.
Chi listens to you.
Tell him to change his statement.
Deny he killed Chung.
Let the Police think because
he's mentally challenged
his statement is not believable.
They'll only charge him for
obstruction of justice.
Then the money is yours.
If that's not enough,
I can sell my gold jewelry and dowry.
It should be worth $7M.
I know you don't care for this family.
After the baby is born, we'll raise it.
Take the money and live the life you want.
Your terms are so attractive.
As opposed to money, sincerity is
more important.
I'm willing to do anything for Chi.
You shouldn't have done that.
I only wanted you to say "please".
Please?
Will you tell Chi to change his statement?
I just remembered, Chi is a murder suspect.
He can only see his lawyer and no one else.
You knelt down for nothing.
You...
I'm bearing you a grandchild.
Don't scare me.
I need to rest for the baby's sake.
See yourself out.
You'll get retribution for this!
What a cocky tramp!
For Chi's sake, here goes nothing...
No, I killed Chung. Arrest me. Go ahead...
Mrs. Cheung, calm down and have a seat.
Just because you claimed to be the killer
doesn't mean we'll arrest you.
The Police only look at the evidence.
You're Cheung Wang-chi's mother.
Your son just pleaded guilty to murder
and you turn yourself in.
Are you taking the rap for him?
I must remind you,
perjury can land you in jail for ten years.
I'm old and I'm a killer.
I don't expect to come out if I go to jail.
I told you I killed Chung...
OK, tell us how exactly did you
kill Cheung Siu-chung.
Like I said before,
I bought sugarcane for Chung that day
and Nam drove me there.
We got into an argument.
It was more than an argument.
When I saw him eating sugarcane,
he was the spitting image
of his grandfather.
He reminded me his grandfather
left me nothing
and had an illegitimate son.
The more I looked at him,
the angrier I became
and I forced the sugarcane into his mouth.
I also scolded him
and told him to keep eating sugarcane
if he liked it so much.
He started to back away
and he rammed into the cabinet.
Then he had a seizure
and lay very still on the floor.
He didn't move like he was dead.
I got scared and left in a hurry.
As I left, I took the new
trust fund document
and I burnt it afterwards.
Because I forced the sugarcane
inside Chung's mouth,
that's why Chung is dead.
Why did you wait this long to
turn yourself in?
Chi is taking the rap for me
because he loves me.
As a mother, I can't watch my son
go to jail.
I killed him, just arrest me.
Cheung Siu-chung's time of death
was at 12:05a.m.
He died of suffocation.
Tang Heung-nam said he drove you home
after 11p.m.
Nam remembered wrong.
Maybe after I forced the sugarcane
inside his mouth,
he lingered till 12:05a.m. to die.
According to our record,
Leung Yuet-ping and Cheung Wang-chi
saw Cheung Siu-chung
half an hour after you left
the village house
and had a fight with him.
That means when you left,
Cheung Siu-chung was still alive.
Leung Yuet-ping didn't go see Chung.
Only Chi went inside.
He must have seen him lying on the floor
and thought he was dead.
Chi is always known to be timid.
He must have been too scared and left.
Why did Leung Yuet-ping lie
about fighting with Cheung Siu-chung
inside the house?
What does she stand to gain from that?
How would I know?
This is Tang Suk-han's statement.
She verified and signed it.
Sir, Grandma was too eager
to save her son,
that's why she pleaded guilty to murder.
Please don't take her seriously.
Ms. Cheung, I know the elderly's mindset.
But she pleaded guilty,
we must detain her according to procedures.
Hello! What's this? I live here.
I need Tang Suk-han to sign for this.
(Cheung Siu-chung)
I'll do it.
Good.
(Sent)
Hello, Di?
Hello, Siu-lai?
My boyfriend parked his car outside
your front door
from 11:30p.m. to 11:45p.m. that night.
He sent you a clip from his dash cam.
See if it's any help to you.
Thank you so much!
Hello, Sze Sir? I found out
the night Chung died, at 11:40p.m.,
he bought something online.
According to my neighbor's boyfriend's
dash cam,
you can clearly see at 11:35p.m.
Grandma got out of Brother Nam's car
and came home.
That means after Grandma came home,
Chung was still alive.
Grandma couldn't have killed him.
Grandma...
Why do you have to be so smart?
You proved I didn't kill Chung,
how can we save Chi?
Grandma, Chung's death was tragic.
I won't let you plead guilty to
something you didn't do
or let Dad go to jail wrongfully.
That night after your fight,
Chung wasn't angry with you.
He bought you a shawl online.
This shawl could prove
after you left that night,
Chung was still alive.
Chung wouldn't want to see
this miscarriage of justice.
Here's the card Chung sent you.
Grandma, don't be mad at me.
It's bad for your health.
This is a designer shawl.
It's expensive but the quality is very good.
I know you didn't want to pay
so much for it.
After I inherit Grandpa's estate,
I promise I'll get you whatever you like
at whatever cost.
Grandma, I love you.
(Till We Meet Again - Reprise)
(Director's words)
Mr. Luk, thanks for giving us
this interview.
You have done so well in China
in recent years.
I'm glad you have not forgotten
your audience in Hong Kong.
Thank you for your time.
Ping...
You still recognize me?
You're afraid I don't recognize you,
that's why you want to run away again.
It happened last year when the play opened.
You left as soon as I saw you.
I was surrounded by reporters
and couldn't catch up with you.
You think...I could have forgotten you?
This play is called Till We Meet Again.
I wrote this play
hoping you'll know how I feel
and come back to me.
I came back for a reprise
hoping you'll come see me again.
I'm staying at the hotel next door.
If you have time,
drop by for a drink and catch up.
Thank you.
Doctor, I'm three months pregnant.
Can I have sex starting today?
Though you are three months pregnant,
you're at an advanced maternal age
and you have high blood pressure.
Sexual activities may affect the fetus
and endanger your life.
I don't recommend it.
Can I have an abortion?
You're over ten weeks,
induced abortion is too risky.
Doc, you just said the pregnancy
is dangerous for me.
So either way is dangerous for me?
I don't really want this baby.
Just get rid of it for me.
Tai-di, how was Chi today?
Too bad I couldn't visit him.
How is he getting on in detention?
He's fine. He just won't give us
straight answers.
Did you find new evidence?
We had to sign the papers for the probate
tomorrow afternoon.
Then the case will go to court.
There's not much time...
Long time no see.
What are you doing here?
Just checking on the house
to see what needs to be fixed.
Tai-di, I'll expand your room on the 3/F
and turn it into my gym room.
What are you talking about?
We're signing the papers tomorrow
at the law firm
and the house will be mine.
I'm here to remind you,
you must pack up and leave.
(Till We Meet Again)
Grandma?
Chung liked plays?
Soon after Grandpa passed away,
Chung told me he went to see a play
with his mother for the first and only time.
That woman never went out with Chung.
What was the name of that play?
Till We Meet Again.
This guy looks familiar.
Luk Chin?
What? Who is he?
He was that tramp's boyfriend before
she married Chi.
An employee at the DAC said
that tramp decided to marry Chi
and pay off her debts,
so she broke up with her loser boyfriend
who was into performing arts.
She went to see this play because of him?
Chung queued up for a long time and
bought expensive tickets
as a treat for his mother.
After he saw it,
he told me excitedly he saw the play
from start to finish.
But that tramp only went there to see
her old flame and not the play.
From start to finish?
No way. He was ten minutes late
for everything.
He couldn't have seen the beginning.
Cut your bad habit of being late.
Or you'll give people an excuse
to use that against you, understand?
Remember we're seeing a movie
the day after tomorrow?
Don't be late.
Even after that time,
when I met him to see a movie,
he was late as usual.
There's no way he was on time
when he saw the play with Leung Yuet-ping.
He wanted his mother to see the whole thing.
He found a way to make sure he was on time.
Grandma...If I can prove something,
there's a chance we can turn things around.
What?
How can I help you, Miss?
I'm the defense counsel in a murder case.
I need you to check something for me.
Ms. Leung, Ms. Tang, Mr. Mok will be
here on time at noon.
Please wait.
Ms. Cheung!
Yes!
We have what you asked for.
Ms. Leung, Ms. Tang,
please read carefully the details of
Mr. Cheung Siu-chung's trust fund.
If you have no questions,
please sign your name.
Right here?
(Leung Yuet-ping)
Hurry up! Stop reading!
Ms. Cheung!
Thank you.
Hurry up! You're wasting Mr. Mok's time.
Hello?
OK...I see...
Signing your name won't get you the house.
What do you mean?
I checked with Chung's smart watch company.
The Police said his heart stopped
at 12:05 a.m. on October 16.
But that was just the time displayed
on Chung's watch.
I just sent you a printout.
Chung set his watch ten minutes ahead.
That means his real time of death
was 11:55 p.m. on October 15.
The time recorded by the watch company
in cloud storage is GMT,
Greenwich Mean Time.
In other words, when Chung died,
he was not yet 21 years old.
He was not entitled to inherit
Grandpa's estate.
The trust fund he set up is invalid.
Grandpa's estate will follow
the Intestates' Estates Ordinance,
and will be divided up between
his spouse and children.
So Grandma and Dad will each get 50%.
Impossible!
Do you know why Chung set his watch
ten minutes early?
He wanted to see the play with you,
so he set the watch ten minutes early.
Chung loved you very much,
but you didn't cherish him
or respect his last wishes.
If you didn't force me to move out,
Tai-di and I would not have found
the tickets to the play
and we wouldn't have known he set
his watch ten minutes early.
You get nothing and you did it to yourself.
Mr. Mok, a picture like this
can be used as proof?
Shouldn't the Police look into it?
It'll depend on whether the court
will admit this as new evidence.
I'm afraid you must both wait a bit longer
to see if Cheung Siu-chung's
trust fund is valid.
Hear that?
I still have a shot at the house.
I don't care. You're moving out.
We'll see.
Chin, I can't go to the cruise terminal
with you today.
All the best. I'll see you in three months.
Bye.
Ping, an abortion at your age
is too dangerous. Don't do it.
I was afraid you didn't want
someone else's baby.
All because I had no money back then.
Or you wouldn't have to marry
someone else to pay off the debts.
You have suffered long enough.
Now that we're finally back together.
I won't mind anything about you.
Besides, I like kids.
I'll raise your child like my own.
Don't worry. Leave everything to me.
What is it?
Madam, a man went through your trash
last night.
He also brought a camera
and he asked me if you went out
with another man.
I didn't say anything.
You're with child, be careful.
Would that be a private detective
hired by Tai-di?
Oh dear! Chin spent the night here.
What if they took pictures of us
and show them to Chi?
Chi would know I cheated on him again
and may tell the Police everything
in a rage.
Chin, scrap that idea.
Let's stick to the original plan.
I'll meet you at the cruise terminal.
Dad, I hired a private detective
who took pictures of
Leung Yuet-ping sleeping with another man
behind your back.
I also went through her trash in the hotel
and found the receipt of an abortion.
She got rid of your baby three months ago.
Dad, look what she did to you and the baby!
She only wanted you to take the rap for her.
Come on, listen to me...
How did Chung B die that night?
Can you tell us the truth?
Sorry, it's time for the trial.
Understand?
Let's go, it's time.
The trial started ten minutes ago.
In another half an hour,
everything will be all over.
Father...
Why did you do something like that?
Why did you do this to me?
(The day before the incident)
Chung...stay right there...
I'll be 21 years old in two days.
I will go home and explain my arrangements
to everyone.
No, stay right there.
Chung, listen to me...
I don't want to listen.
I don't want to see you again.
(The day of the incident)
Did Chung contact you?
No.
He'll be 21 years old tomorrow.
You want to celebrate with him?
Yes!
Then send him a message.
Tell him you missed him, ask for his address
and we'll surprise him and
celebrate with him, OK?
Great...
(Papa, I'm at No. 38 Wan Mei Village)
(I'll be waiting for you)
Get up...didn't you want to celebrate
Chung's birthday with him?
I'm very sleepy.
It's cool, what is that?
Hello? I need a car from Ko Cho Village
to Wan Mei Village.
I need a car from Ko Cho Village
What's wrong? You're scratching all over.
I feel itchy.
Stop. Scratching will make it itchier.
Oh dear, I forgot mint will make you itchy.
Now my leg is itchy.
Up ahead on Man Nin Street,
get him something from the
convenience store.
Thanks.
Take this...
Drink some water.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Chung B!
Papa!
I missed you so much.
Papa is not angry with you.
Will you come home with me?
Good...
I don't mean to pressure you.
I don't want Grandma in the house,
because I have bad memories there.
I don't want to live there anymore.
Let's sell the house,
and buy two separate flats.
One for the three of us,
the other one for Grandma.
Won't that be better?
Good idea...
If you don't like bad memories of the house,
let Grandma stay there.
We'll move to somewhere smaller, OK?
Chung B is so smart!
What can I say to make you understand?
It's 12 o'clock...
Chung B, it's 12 o'clock!
You're 21 years old...
12 o'clock already?
Happy birthday...
Thanks, Papa...
Cheung Wang-chi, can you describe
Cheung Siu-chung's relationship with
his mother Leung Yuet-ping?
You can't let Grandma stay in the house.
No, I won't abandon Grandma!
But you will abandon me?
I'll be home tomorrow to
explain my decision.
Chung B, what's wrong?
He's having a seizure.
Papa will save you...Bite on this...
It's after midnight, Chung is 21 years old.
If he's dead, I can take the revised
document of the trust fund.
Then I can get the house.
No, don't pull it out!
He's still having a seizure.
What now?
Stick it back in!
He's that old geezer's son,
I gave birth to him for the money.
I'll get the money when he's dead.
I must leave this place.
I can pretend the past didn't happen.
Chung, I can finally forget about you.
Why would a mother abandon her baby?
How could Honey kill the baby?
Did she want Chung B to die?
Chung is dead...
How did that happen?
I wanted to save him.
How did I kill him?
Chi, listen to me. You wanted to save Chung.
You applied too much force and killed him.
You didn't mean it.
The Police should not put you in jail, OK?
Don't let anyone know we saw Chung.
Or else people would think
we're connected to Chung's death.
Don't tell anyone.
Listen to me, we did not see Chung.
We did not see the revised document.
We were asleep at home at the time, OK?
Change into your pajamas and go to bed.
Open the door!
What is it?
Tai-di just called.
Something bad happened to Chung.
They're giving him emergency resuscitation.
What?
She wanted me to wake you.
Chi...
OK...I'll help him change. Go downstairs.
Chi, I'll go to the hospital.
Go to sleep. Don't worry.
I thought you would save Chung B,
but you did not.
You wanted to kill Chung B.
You meant to...kill Chung B.
It's OK, Grandma...
Defendant, you need to calm down...
Bring Leung Yuet-ping in.
Since the defendant is currently
emotionally unstable,
the court will take a recess.
Miss, what happened?
My stomach hurts...
Shall I get you an ambulance?
No, I'll just rest up a bit...
I put up with the Cheungs for over 20 years
for the money.
I can't turn back.
I can't leave without the money.
Mom!
What?
My first medal at Sports Day...for you.
I got my first pay cheque.
I bought you a bracelet.
Do you know why Chung set his watch
ten minutes early?
He wanted to see the play with you,
so he set the watch ten minutes early.
Chung loved you very much,
but you didn't cherish him.
Dad, I don't know if you can understand me,
Leung Yuet-ping had pre-eclampsia
and triggered an epileptic seizure.
She passed away yesterday.
So she's dead...like Chung B?
She left us and became a star?
We'll never see her again?
Because new evidence has been submitted,
the current jury is dismissed for a retrial.
Regarding the manslaughter charge
against Cheung Wang-chi,
will the jury please give us the verdict?
Your Honor, the verdict is unanimous.
We find the defendant Cheung Wang-chi
not guilty of manslaughter.
Luckily, Tai-di took care of everything.
Or I wouldn't know how to carry out
Chung's last wishes.
Burial at sea is very simple.
Just apply for it online.
Chung BB...
There is justice after all.
Heaven took your mother
but left you with us.
Luckily the mother was rushed in
just in time,
we managed to save the baby.
We can carry on the family line.
Chung BB, Chung B loved to swim.
Grandma and Tai-di are taking him
for a swim.
He should be thrilled.
(A few months before the incident)
A ghost!
Stop it! That's enough!
She's scared! Get lost!
Miss, are you OK?
I'm fine.
Can you get up?
I'll carry you.
What?
Come on!
Really? What's your name?
I'm Ngai Ka-yan. And you?
Cheung Tai-di.
Why hasn't he called?
What?
Did you see the footage I sent you?
How could you let people trick you?
What trick? Someone scared me.
Hurry up and take a look.
Stop it! That's enough!
She's scared!
(Middle-aged woman in heat)
What the hell? How could they do this?
What bloody show is this?
J Weekly?!